LORETTA CAIN

♦ JUNIOR FRONT END WEB DEVELOPER ♦

locacodes@gmail.com

lcain.github.io

0424 353 529

SOCIAL

t

locacodes.tumblr.com/



@locacodes

in

linkedin.com/in/loretta-cain-34b4b7110

PROFILE

I am a junior front end web developer who loves creating engaging and interactive web applications. I am currently seeking a role where I can use my 10 years of customer services experience to collaboratively create better user experiences on the web. I have a passion for learning and a naturally curious nature. I am constantly striving to discover new things.

SKILLS

JavaScript

- · Ruby on Rails
- jQuery
- Underscore
- HTML
- CSS
- GitHub/Heroku
- Phaser

- Conflict Resolution
- Communication
- Management
- Public Speaking
- Training
- Empathy
- AutoCAD
- Tessitura

EDUCATION

Nov 2015 -

Feb 2016

Web Development Immersive - General Assembly Operational use of Javascript, jQuery, Phaser, Ruby, Rails, HTML5, CSS, Github, Heroku, PostGresSQL Working knowledge of SCSS, JSON, Node.js, HAML,

Backbone, D3. js, Three. js

July 2012 -Dec 2013

Diploma of Civil Engineering Design - TAFE

Risk Assessments, Project Management, Break Down Structure, Estimating, Development Applications

January 2014

Certificate IV Occupational Health and Safety

(BSB41412) - EasyHR

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

General Assembly

Team Lead Nov 2015 - Feb 2016

- Lead a team of four in the creation of Space Race Evolution, a shooter style game with twelve levels created in JavaScript that evolves as you play
- Selected and mastered the libraries required for the project, and demonstrated their use to the other developers
- Oversaw all aspects of building the Rails backend for users and high scores
- Ensured the team communicated clearly throughout the project, were up to date with current goals, and worked as group when committing changes

Sydney Theatre Company

- -Customer Services Supervisor
- -Work Health and Safety Advisor

May 2010 - October 2015

- Supervised and trained a team of 20
- Managed multiple live events across multiple venues simultaneously, responsible for customer services for up to 900 patrons a night
- Liaised and fostered relationships between STC and other institutions (Sydney Opera House, Sydney Festival, Sydney Dance Company, Sydney Writer's Festival, and other outside hirers)
- Conflict and complaint resolution, entrusted with banking and cash handling for the company
- Work Health and Safety Representative and Advisor, First Aider and Fire Warden

Australian Brandenburg Orchestra

-Customer Services Representative Dec 2014 - October 2015

- Created subscriptions, assisted patrons with general and technical enquiries via phone, email, or in person
- Following up with any errors or account problems
- · Data entry and database cleaning
- · Reporting to the duty manager on a daily basis and recording data in excel